翻译：可恶的大马猴
特效：可恶的大马猴
是辆电动车
All right, we got an EV!
铺设两条水带
Let's get two attack lines going now!
禁止商用 转载请标明出处
队长 火好像还没烧到电动车
Looks like the fire hasn't reached the EV yet, Cap.
对 但没必要烧到
Yeah, it doesn't need to.
现在的温度足够把电池煮爆了
The heat's enough to cook the battery.
再过大概五分钟 就会发生热失控
In about five minutes, we're looking at a thermal runaway.
电池内部因热量累积 导致温度急剧升高 最终引发燃烧或爆炸的过程
要不要先用热成像仪
Should we check the battery with the thermal imaging
- 检测一下电池情况 - 不用 先确保现场安全
- camera first? - No, first, we make things safe.
听着 立刻设置警戒区域
All right? I want you to get me a perimeter.
- 路锥全摆上 - 收到 队长
- Cones all around! - Copy that, Cap!
迪亚兹 那辆车里还有其他人吗
All right, Diaz, anyone else in that car?
- 确认完毕 队长 只有一个 - 好的
- All clear, Cap. Only one. - Okay.
- 撑住 伙计 - 给他来点氧气
- I've got you, buddy. - Let's get him on some O2.
我这里有个被困的受害者 电池还在升温
All right, I got a trapped victim and a battery cooking.
拉维 对电动车喷水
Ravi, get me a water curtain on that EV.
- 让它降温 - 马上就来
- Keep it cool. - Coming up!
- 巴克 - 我在 队长
- Buck! - Right here, Cap!
女士 这是液压剪
Ma'am, steel jaws!
我的天
Oh, my God.
好了 队长 我们把她弄出来了 担架
Okay. Cap, we got her. Gurney!
干得漂亮 各位
Okay, good work, everyone.
把伤者抬上担架后
Once we get our friend on a gurney,
我们就往后撤
we're gonna pull back.
全体队员做好防御准备
All crew set for defense.
重复 全体队员做好防御准备
I repeat, all crew set for defense.
准备完毕
All set.
不
No!
- 麦迪 - 别指望我
- Maddie - Don't you look to me
来安慰你 你害死了我儿子
for comfort. You murdered my son!
紧急呼救
第九季 第十集
小心处理
你起得真早
You're up early.
你也一样
Mm. So are you.
我答应吉允要给她做煎饼
I promised Jee I'd make her pancakes.
已经做好了
Already done.
而且 我还给你们俩做了午餐
Plus, I made lunch for both you guys,
还给小纳什做了点果泥
and a little purée for Baby Nash.
昨晚没睡吗
So you didn't sleep?
睡了 但挺后悔的
I did, and I have regrets.
你想聊聊吗
Do you want to talk about them?
这事倒还犯不着找精神科医生
Well, don't really have to call Sigmund Freud on this one.
西格蒙德·弗洛伊德 奥地利犹太裔神经学家、心理学家
因为新来的菜鸟做噩梦
I'm having nightmares about my new probie.
这梦到什么了 火灾还是水灾
So what was it this time? Fire or flood?
肇事逃逸 还撞见雅典娜 不过这事
Hit and run, with a side of Athena, but we really should
- 咱们得先搁一搁 - 好吧
- put a pin in that one. - Okay.
等哈里正式上岗 你说不定能睡安稳些
Maybe you'll sleep easier when Harry starts.
他今天第一天报到 对吧
I mean, today's his first day, right?
你怎么看起来慌慌的
Why do you seem scared?
我记得你挺希望哈里来118分队的
I thought you wanted Harry in the 118.
是啊 但现在有点后悔让他来了
Yeah, I did, but now I think I'm having captain's remorse.
放心吧 你会尽全力保护好他的
Hey, you are gonna keep him as safe as anyone can.
希望我能做到吧
If anyone can.
你们说要来吃早餐
When you guys said you wanted to come over
我还真没想到
for breakfast, I wasn't expecting anything
- 居然这么隆重 - 这可是
- this elaborate. - Well, you're looking at
为哈里准备的庆祝早餐
Harry's congratulatory breakfast
庆祝他在118队上岗的第一天
for his first day at the 118.
- 那 哈里人呢 - 问得好
- So... where's Harry? - Exactly.
我一大早就起来做饭了
I got up early to cook.
我起得更早 过来帮忙做饭
And I got up even earlier to come over to help cook.
结果我们俩还没起床
Except he had already left before either
他人就先走了
of us had even gotten out of bed.
说是要给大家留个好印象
Something about making a good first impression.
弄了这么多吃的 我都不知道咋办了
I just didn't know what to do with all the food.
哈里不在正好便宜我了
Well, Harry's loss is my gain.
给我一个煎饼
Pass me them pancakes.
♪ 一寸一寸 一滴一滴 ♪
♪ Measure by measure, drop by drop♪
♪ 一磅一磅 我们清点存货  ♪
♪ And pound for pound, we're taking stock...♪
♪ 停 停 停  ♪
♪ Stop, stop, stop...♪
队长 要来杯摩卡吗
Hey, Cap, you want a mocha?
我不喝牛奶巧克力 而且你不是应该
Chocolate milk is for children. And shouldn't you
去给消防车补充物资吗 新来的菜鸟会以为
be stocking the rigs? Our new probie's gonna think
118分队全是懒鬼
the 118 is full of slackers.
新来的菜鸟已经把消防物资补好了
Probie already stocked the rig.
他已经来了
He's already here?
早上五点就来了 我们这些老菜鸟真是自愧不如
Since 5:00 a.m. Putting us ex-probies to shame.
- 我在这儿 队长 - 不
- Right here, Cap. - No.
我来的时候
And by the time I got in,
他已经整理完杂物
he'd already completed a mess run
还洗了两大筐衣服
and two loads of laundry.
是吗 那这是什么
Oh, really. And what is this?
要点的咖啡 来点什么吗 队长
It's coffee orders. You want something, Cap?
拉维说你喜欢街角那家
Ravi said you like that spot down the street.
行 我确实想喝点
Yes. Yes, I do want something.
非常感谢 不过
Thank you very much, but, uh,
还是让拉维去帮我买吧
Ravi here is gonna get it for me.
让我去 可他才是菜鸟啊
Me? Uh, but he's the probie.
你想让他第一天上班就被烫伤吗
You want him scalding himself on his first day?
- 不太想 - 他一绊
- Not particularly? - He trips,
杯盖一滑 嘭的一下
the lid slips, bam.
三度烫伤
Third-degree burns,
都赖巴克利的摩卡
all courtesy of Buckley's mocha.
所以 我得派个更有经验的人去
No, I'm sending someone with more experience.
更有 买咖啡经验
More experience... getting coffee.
队长 我在咖啡店干过
Cap, I... I worked at a coffee shop.
确实 咖啡是他唯一的工作经验
Yeah, coffee is the only work experience he has.
别担心 哈里 拉维能搞定
Don't worry about it, Harry. Ravi's got this.
好了 菜鸟 第一次出警 走吧
Okay. Here we go, rookie. First call.
这就对了 我们走
That's what I'm talking about. Let's go.
要不还是算了吧
Or let's stay.
队长
Cap?
你今天早上够忙的了
You've had a big morning.
这样吧 你留下来待命 好吗
You know what? Better that you hang back, okay?
那你们出勤时我该做什么
Uh, what should I do while you're gone?
歇会儿 打个盹 或者看看电视
Just take a break or a nap, you know? Maybe watch some TV.
电视
TV?
这班值下来挺久的 听我的
Yeah, it's a long shift. You know what?
得劳逸结合
You should pace yourself.
收到
Copy that.
里德
Reid?
- 哇哦 - 里德
- Bah! - Reid?
宝贝 快下来 你会伤到自己的
Baby, get down. You'll hurt yourself.
妈妈 我是超人里德
Mom, I'm SuperReid.
从不受伤
I never get hurt.
那也会磕到的
Okay, you'll get injured.
我能帮忙吗
Oh, can I help?
小心点
Careful.
宝贝 你和刀子可合不来
Sweetie, you and knives don't mix.
超人有保护罩
Superman has a force field.
但你去急诊的次数都快能办会员卡了
You practically have a punch card at urgent care.
你从来不让我做有意思的事
You never let me do anything fun.
- 不准摔跤 - 那是格斗
- No wrestling. - It's sanctioned combat.
- 不准踢足球 - 加了个球的摔跤
- No football. - Wrestling, plus a ball.
不准溜冰
No roller-skating.
谁说要溜冰了
Who said anything about roller-skating?
兰斯的生日派对
Lance's birthday party.
他说你肯定不让我去
He said you probably won't let me come.
宝贝
Baby...
你可没跟我说兰斯要办派对
you never said anything about Lance having a party.
那我能去吗
So I can go?
里德 妈妈最重要的职责是什么
Reid, what's my most important job?
保护我的安全
To keep me safe.
但超人可以保护自己
But Superman can keep himself safe.
等你长大点 你也可以
And someday you'll be able to do that, too.
在那之前 咱们俩得一起
Until then, it's you and me.
好吗
Okay?
就像蝙蝠侠和罗宾
Like Batman and Robin.
DC漫画中最著名的英雄搭档
我就知道你不让我去
I knew you'd say no.
我是唯一不能去的小孩
I'm the only kid not going!
你和别的孩子不一样
You're not other kids.
他们觉得我是个怪胎
They think I'm a freak.
太危险了
It's too dangerous.
我恨你
I hate you!
随便你怎么恨
Hate me all you want.
但我是你妈妈
But I am your mother,
我会不惜一切代价保护你
and I will protect you no matter what.
妈妈
Mom?
妈妈 我没事
Mom, I'm okay.
妈妈
Mom?
Mom!
911接线员
这里是911 请问有什么紧急情况
来电人
救救我妈妈
好的 我是来帮助你的 你妈妈怎么了
Okay, I'm here to help. What's going on with your mom?
她一动不动 我们家着火了
She's not moving! Our house is on fire!
在皇后街1812号
1812 Queen Street.
消防员已经在路上了 我叫麦迪
Firefighters are on their way. I'm Maddie.
- 你叫什么名字 - 里德
- What's your name? - Reid.
请救救我们 火太大了
Please help us. There's so much fire.
- 火从墙里窜出来了 - 听起来像是
- It's shooting out of the wall! - It sounds like
燃气管道泄漏 你说你妈妈一动不动
a gas line. You said your mom's not moving?
我觉得她撞到脑袋了
I think she hit her head.
她不动了 妈妈 求你了
She won't move. Mom, please.
快起来啊 家里着火了 妈妈
Mom, you got to get up. The house is on fire! Mom.
求求你 你答应过我的
Please. You promised.
我们要像蝙蝠侠和罗宾一样 对吧
You and me, like Batman and Robin, right?
里德 你能走到前门那里吗
Reid, do you have a path to the front door?
- 能 - 我需要你出去
- Yeah. - I need you to go.
跑到屋外 挥动双手
Run outside, wave your arms
这样消防员就能看到你
so firefighters can see you.
我不能丢下妈妈
I'm not leaving my mom!
里德 妈妈也希望你平平安安的
Reid, she would want you to be safe.
快从房子里出来
I need you to get out of the house.
不
No!
那你家里有灭火器吗
Okay, do you have a fire extinguisher?
在柜子里
In the cabinet!
你找到了吗
Did you find it?
里德
Reid?
麦迪 燃气灶原来的位置 有个阀门
Maddie, there's a knob here where the stove was.
那是燃气总阀
That's the gas shutoff.
它着火了
It's on fire.
那就退后 别管它
Then step back. Leave it alone.
但关了它就能止住大火 对吗
But it'll stop the big fire, right?
里德 别碰那个阀门 很烫
Reid, do not touch that knob! It's red hot.
里德
Reid?!
我要动手了
Here goes.
别 别碰 里德 听我说
No, no, no, don't! Reid, listen to me.
消防员马上就到了
The firefighters are almost there.
里德 你还在吗
Reid, are you there?
里德
Reid,
你没事吧
are you okay?
成功了
It worked!
成功了 我没事
It worked! I feel fine.
你为什么要把手伸进火里
Why would you stick your hand into the fire?
你知道那有多危险吗
Do you know how dangerous that is?
我知道 可是家里着火了
I guess, but the house was on fire.
你这孩子 可真勇敢 肯定疼死了
You're tough as nails, pal. This must hurt like heck.
并不疼
Not really.
- 我什么都感觉不到 - 里德不是普通孩子
- Nothing hurts me. - Reid's not your average kid.
他有先天性
He has CIP. Congenital
痛觉缺失症
Insensitivity to Pain. Yeah.
极为罕见的遗传性神经系统疾病 患者先天无法感知物理疼痛
- 这很罕见 - 是的
- Wow, that's pretty rare. - Yeah.
我也是后来才知道的
So I've learned.
保护他 不让他伤到自己
Protecting him from himself
就是我的全职工作
is my full-time job.
他感觉不到疼痛 愁死人了
He feels no pain, and it's a pain in the butt.
- 今天这是超能力 - 好了 队长
- Well, today it was a superpower. - Okay, Cap.
厨房排查完毕
Kitchen's overhauled.
- 你 处理得很好 干得不错 - 谢谢
- You, great work on that gas line. Good job. - Thanks.
- 你救了你的房子 - 还有你的妈妈
- You saved your house. - Not to mention your mom.
好了 准备撤离
All right, let's load up and go.
慢慢来 孩子
All right, nice and easy, buddy.
好的
Okay.
- 尽量别乱动 好吗 - 好的
- Try and keep this still, okay? - Okay.
小心点 小家伙 别被斗篷绊倒了
Careful, kiddo. Don't trip on your cape.
妈妈 我没事
Mom, I'm fine.
你不可能事事都保护得了他们
Can't protect 'em from everything.
这里是911 请问有什么紧急情况
911. What's your emergency?
我在五旬节圣堂祈祷会教堂
I'm at the Church of the Pentecostal Temple of Prayer!
魔鬼附身了阿比盖尔姊妹
The devil has entered Sister Abigail.
我们正在为她驱魔
We were exorcising the demons from her,
现在魔鬼又咬住了以撒弟兄
and now, the devil's got his teeth in Brother Isaac!
我们赶到现场时 那名年轻女孩被绑在
When we arrived, the young woman was on a table...
一张桌子上
...in restraints.
血压和心率
Her blood pressure and heart rate
都很高 而且身体
were elevated, and her body was
剧烈抽搐
spasming severely.
但你们接到的求助电话
But the call you were responding to
并没有提到这些情况
didn't mention any of that?
报警人只说她咬伤了牧师
We were told she had bitten the minister.
但我们到了现场才意识到
But when we got there, we realized
事情远不止如此
there was something else going on.
是什么导致一个十七岁的女孩
What would cause a 17-year-old girl
去咬一个成年男人
to bite a grown man?
破伤风
It was tetanus.
由破伤风梭菌引起的严重急性神经系统感染疾病
会导致肌肉强直性抽搐和呼吸困难
也就是下颌僵硬症 是一种
Lockjaw. A bacterial
细菌性感染 通常由穿刺伤引发
infection usually caused by some kind of puncture wound.
阿比盖尔是怎么受这种伤的
How did Abigail get such a wound?
她 住的那个房间
The room she was... staying in.
有一张老旧的金属床架
There was an old, metal bed frame.
床尾的栏杆断了
The footboard was broken.
如果她的破伤风
What was the likely outcome
没有得到治疗 结果会怎样
if her tetanus had remained untreated?
呼吸困难 肺炎
Trouble breathing, pneumonia,
抽搐导致的骨折
broken bones from the spasms
甚至可能死亡
and possibly death.
谢谢你 威尔逊消防员
Thank you, Firefighter Wilson.
你有十五年的医护经验
You have 15 years of experience as a medic.
对吗
Is that correct?
是的
Yes.
和你当父母的经验相比 是多还是少
Is that more or less experience than you've had as a parent?
当父母更多是凭直觉
I parent with my gut.
成功远多于失败
I succeed more than I fail.
我有时是否对孩子保护过度 当然
Do I keep my son too close from time to time? Sure.
但我有没有把他绑在桌子上
But do I tie him up to a table?
有没有把他锁在小房间里
Do I lock him in a cell?
绝对不会
Hell no.
你是不是个很容易愤怒的人
Aren't you a very angry man,
迪亚兹消防员
Firefighter Diaz?
曾经是
I used to be.
你不是曾因一个
Weren't you cited
让我看看 停车位问题
for assaulting a man over let's see here
而被指控袭击他人
a parking spot?
- 那是因为 - 这正能说明
- That was - Emblematic of the violent temper
你对我当事人施加的暴力行为
you exercised against my clients while on the scene.
- 我没有施暴 - 你的言语粗暴
- I was not violent. - Verbally abusive.
造成了不必要的精神伤害
Causing undue emotional distress.
彻头彻尾的恐吓
Downright intimidation!
这根本不是事实
That's not true.
也正因如此 这影响了他们随后
That is what colored any subsequent statements
向警方做的所有陈述
from them to the police.
我们以后能别
Can we please never
- 再经历这种事了 - 借你吉言
- do that again? - From your lips.
阿比盖尔
Abigail.
很高兴见到你
It's good to see you.
我一直没机会向你道谢
I never got the chance to say thank you.
我想你当时有很多事要处理
I think you had a lot going on.
你能好起来 我们就很开心了
And we're just happy you're back on your feet.
- 是啊 - 威尔逊消防员
- Yeah. - Firefighter Wilson,
借一步说话
can I borrow you for a minute?
保重
Take care.
谢谢
Thank you.
阿比盖尔 你今天表现得特别棒
Hey, you did a great job today, Abigail.
敢于反抗他们 非常勇敢
Uh, standing up to them is incredibly brave.
你是怎么做到的
How did you do it?
做到
Do...
什么
what?
不那么 愤怒
Learn to be less... angry.
靠时间
Time.
靠心理治疗
Therapy.
一次又一次的治疗
More therapy.
家人朋友的陪伴也很重要
Having friends and family helps.
有人一直拉着我别走偏 帮了很大忙
You know, keeping me on the right path helped a lot, too.
至少我还有时间
Well, at least I've got the time part.
至于别的
The rest?
我连油钱都快付不起了 更别说做心理治疗了
Can't really afford therapy when I can barely afford gas.
我记得你之前在寄养体系里
Thought you were in the foster care system.
- 他们没有提供援助吗 - 我满十八岁了
- Don't they have resources? - I turned 18.
寄养中心给了我一张生日贺卡
Foster care gave me a birthday card
还有一张去外婆家的公交车票
and a bus ticket to my grandmother's.
外婆把车丢给我 让我自己走人
She gave me her car to get rid of me.
我就一直睡在车里
I've been sleeping in it.
这就是被解救后的小小代价
That's the small downside to being rescued.
当然 再也没人会伤害你了 但
There is no one left to hurt you, sure, but...
这也意味着 真的一个人都没有了
...that's because there's nobody left at all.
总会有人在乎你的
Well, there are people who care about you.
在哪呢
Where?
- 怎么样 - 这个嘛 非常复杂
- How was it? - It was, uh, very complex.
相当棘手
Touch and go.
两个孩子的牙套缠在一起了
Two kids had their braces stuck together.
埃迪回来了吗
Hey, did Eddie make it back yet?
是的 他还带了个朋友回来
Uh, yeah, yeah, and he brought a friend with him.
嗨 各位
Hey, guys.
你们还记得阿比盖尔吧
You remember Abigail.
当然
Of course.
我倒希望我也记得你们
I wish I could say the same.
那天我唯一记得的就是
The only thing I remember from that day is
埃迪的脸
Eddie's face.
这位是韩队长 这位是巴克 那位是拉维
Oh, this is Captain Han, that's Buck, and that's Ravi.
真的不知道该怎么感谢你们
I can't tell you how much I appreciate this.
你已经救过我一次了
You've already saved my life once.
现在感觉你又救了我一次
Now I feel like you're saving it again.
这是我们的职责 埃迪 能跟你说句话吗
Well, it's what we do. Eddie, can I get a word?
我得跟你聊聊那件事
I need to talk to you about that thing.
- 失陪一下 - 当然 队长
- Pardon us. - Sure, Cap.
他有麻烦了吗
Is he in trouble?
有麻烦
Uh, trouble, no.
不 没有
No, he-he's not.
我不希望他有麻烦 他对我特别好
I'd hate for him to be. He's been so kind to me.
他看我无家可归 就把我带到这儿了
He saw I didn't have any place to go, so he brought me here.
平时都是巴克把流浪的小动物带回来
It's usually Buck who brings in the strays.
我不是说你是流浪的小动物
Not that you're a stray.
不 我就是
No. That's exactly what I am.
这辈子 我身边就只有爸妈
My whole life, it was just me and my mom and my dad,
可现在
and...
一个都没了
now there's nobody.
阿比盖尔 总会有人陪着你的
Hey, there's always somebody, Abigail.
家人并不仅只是血缘上的亲人
Family isn't just the people you're born to.
也是那些你主动选择的人
It's also the people you choose.
她现在无依无靠
She's got nobody.
她需要帮助
She needs help.
我只是担心 她需要的那种帮助
I'm just afraid the kind of help she needs,
在这里我们给不了
we can't give it to her here.
所以我才叫了后援
Which is why I brought backup.
艾丽克斯
Alex.
迪亚兹消防员
Firefighter Diaz.
那是谁
Who's that?
她是艾丽克斯
That's Alex.
阿比盖尔 这位是艾丽克斯·道尔
Abigail, this is Alex Doyle.
洛杉矶警局SMART项目的成员 全称是
She's part of LAPD's SMART program, which stands for
- 系统性 - 全市心理评估应对小组
- Systematic... - Systemwide Mental Assessment Response Team.
- 是的 - 你觉得我精神有问题
- Yeah. - You think I'm mental?
我知道你经历了很多
I think you've been through a lot.
我的工作之一 就是帮助人们
And part of my job is to connect people
联系到他们需要的资源 让他们能重新好好生活
to the resources they need to get them back on their feet.
我听说
I, um... I understand
你最近无家可归
that you've been dealing with some homelessness?
我一直住在我外婆的车里
I've been living in my grandmother's car.
艾丽克斯会帮你找个地方住
Alex is going to help you find a place to stay.
其实 我已经找好了
Actually, I... I already did.
真的
You did?
在哪
Where?
帕萨迪纳那边的过渡性住房
Faith-based transitional housing in Pasadena.
那里有心理咨询服务 还有大学预科辅导
They have, uh, counseling and college prep.
你可以先住一晚 要是觉得好 也可以多住些日子
You can stay the night, or longer if you like it.
你觉得怎么样 阿比盖尔
What do you say, Abigail?
我不知道
I don't know.
我们可以顺路给你买点洗漱用品
We can stop and-and get you some toiletries.
再买几双新袜子
Maybe some fresh socks?
我不需要袜子
I don't need socks.
就让这位好心的女士给你买几双
Uh, why don't you let the nice lady buy you some socks?
好不好
Okay?
- 好吧 - 好的
- Okay. - Okay.
911接线员
这里是911 请问有什么紧急情况
来电人
我爸爸失踪了
先生 我叫麦迪
Okay, sir, my name's Maddie.
我需要了解一些信息
I'm gonna need some information.
我是安德鲁 我爸爸叫比尔
I'm Andrew. My dad's name is Bill.
全名叫威廉·施耐德
Uh, uh, William Schneider.
他八十七岁了
He's, uh, 87.
身高一米九二 白色头发 绿色眼睛
Uh, six-four, white hair, green eyes.
他肯定是自己走丢的
He must have just wandered off.
我觉得他自己都不知道要去哪
Uh, I mean, I don't even think he knows where he's going.
你觉得他可能是迷路了
You think he might have gotten lost?
他肯定是搞糊涂了
He must have gotten confused.
我真应该盯紧点他的
Ah, I should have been watching him closer.
他最后出现的位置是哪里
What was his last known location?
他家 切斯特街104号
Uh, his house, 104 Chester Street.
我现在就在他家
Uh, I'm-I'm here now.
公共紧急寻人预警机制 主要用于寻找走失的老年人
所有单位注意 发布银色警报 寻找威廉·施耐德
All units, starting a Silver Alert for William Schneider.
目标可能意识不清 先生 请留在你父亲家里 好吗
May be disoriented. Sir, don't leave your dad's house, okay?
我们派了最优秀的人员去找他
We have the best people working to find him.
安德鲁·施耐德
Andrew Schneider?
你来得真快
You got here fast.
请进
Please come in.
还是没收到你父亲的消息吗
Uh, so, still no word from your father?
没有 我梳理了一下时间线
No. I worked up a timeline.
昨天下午六点 我还跟他通了电话 跟往常一样
I spoke to him yesterday at 6:00 p.m. like we always do,
今早的监控里 最后看到他是
and then, uh, this morning, I have him on the cameras
上午的11点56分
up until, uh, 11:56 a.m.
你 呃
Oh, you, uh,
真是把他看得死死的
really keep an eye on him, huh?
没办法 我必须得这么做
Yeah, well, I have to.
他死活不肯去养老院
I mean, he refuses to go into assisted living.
- 手机还总忘充电 - 好的
- And he never remembers to charge his phone. - Okay.
那监控显示到上午11点56分之前 他在做什么
So what was he doing on the cameras up until 11:56?
上午 就是
A.m. Yes. Uh, just
到处瞎转悠
puttering around.
坐在电脑前玩纸牌游戏
I mean, uh, playing solitaire on his desktop.
- 就是平常那些事 - 嗯
- I mean, just the usual. - Hmm.
然后 监控突然断线了
And then, the-the cameras, they just cut out.
我收到监控的断线提醒
I got a notification when they went down,
立马给他打电话
and so I tried to call him.
他一直没接 我就赶紧开车过来了
He never picked up, and then I just got in the car.
他有手机吗
Does he have a cell phone?
是个翻盖手机
It's a flip phone.
应用程序对他来说太麻烦了
I mean, apps are just asking for trouble.
我到这儿的时候 发现他的手机放在桌子上
When I got here, I found his phone on his desk.
当然是没电了
Dead, of course.
还有这个
Oh, uh, and, uh, this.
他的紧急呼救器
Oh, his Life Alert.
你有没有理由怀疑是有人作案
Well, do you have any reason to suspect foul play?
没有 我爸是个退休的数学老师
No. I mean, Dad's a retired math teacher.
他不开车 也几乎不出门
I mean, he doesn't drive, he barely leaves the house.
你介意我四处看看吗
Well, uh, do you mind if I have a look around?
不介意 请便
Uh, no. Please.
他什么东西都会打印出来
Uh, he, uh, he prints everything.
邮件 文章 我觉得
Emails, articles. I think, uh,
把东西打印出来能帮他记住事情
having hard copies helps him remember things.
谢丽尔·沙利文是谁
Who's Cheryl Sullivan?
我不知道
I have no idea.
这是什么 是机票吗
What is that? Is that a plane ticket?
是收据 六百美元
Receipt. $600.
还升了头等舱
Upgraded to first class.
这太不对劲了
No, this doesn't make sense.
他根本不认识这个女人
He doesn't know who this woman is.
她的航班一小时后就降落了
Her flight lands in an hour.
他肯定是疯了
He has lost his mind.
这就是你家摄像头断线的原因
Here's why your cameras went out.
他把插头拔了
He unplugged it.
我都不知道他还认识路由器
I didn't even know he knew what a router was.
你说过你父亲不开车
You said that your father doesn't drive.
那他有车吗
But does he own a car?
我几个月前就把他车的钥匙拿走了
I took his keys away months ago.
那辆车现在在哪儿
Where is that car now?
谢天谢地 还在这儿
Oh, thank God. It's still here.
这里平常停的是什么车
What's usually parked here?
先生 请靠边停车
Sir, pull your vehicle to the curb.
比尔 洛杉矶警察
Bill? LAPD.
我们一直在找你
We've been looking for you.
我不聋
I'm not deaf.
就是不想理你
I'm ignoring you.
肯定是我儿子让你们来的吧
I assume my boy sent you.
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
我是格兰特警长
My name's Sergeant Grant.
比尔 你知道自己现在在哪吗
Bill, do you know where you are?
离洛杉矶机场直线距离大概五英里
Mm, about five miles from LAX as the crow flies.
那你知道自己在开什么吗
And do you know what you're driving?
知道
Yes.
我还知道我出发时加了六夸脱的油
And I also know that I started with six quarts of gas.
所以 只要你别再拦着我
So that, unless you continue to waylay me,
那我还能顺路去林肯大街的花店买束花
I should have enough to pop by the florist on Lincoln
然后再去见我的女性朋友
before I meet my lady friend.
比尔
Bill...
你离家很远了
you're a long way from home.
要的就是这效果
Yeah, that's the idea.
你干嘛把我当成失踪人口一样问话
Why are you talking to me like I'm on a milk carton?
你儿子 他觉得
Your son he implied
我老糊涂了
That I've lost my marbles?
你看我像糊涂的样子吗
Well, you can see that I haven't.
不如行个方便让我过去
So how about you just let me pass along?
比尔 我们都清楚 这东西根本不能上路
Bill, we both know that thing's not street legal.
但它开起来感觉真不赖
But it edges like a dream.
比尔 你可能神志清醒
Bill, you may be in your right mind,
但你儿子快为你担心死了
but your son is losing his worrying about you.
你知道吗 他把我当小孩一样对待
You know, he treats me like a child.
他只是希望自己的父亲能平平安安
All he wants is for his father to be safe.
我不能强迫你回家
Now, I can't force you to go home,
但我会扣押你的割草机
but I will impound your lawn mower.
行
Okay.
- 拷我吧 - 呃
- Cuff me. - Uh...
你没有被逮捕 比尔
You're not under arrest, Bill.
但你还是要带我回监狱
But you're still taking me to prison.
你在想什么
What were you thinking?
为什么要开割草机去机场兜风
Why would you joyride to the airport on a lawn mower?
你拿走了我的车钥匙
You took my car keys.
- 因为你把车撞坏了 - 是某个笨蛋
- Because you wrecked the car. - Some knucklehead
用购物车撞了我的车
banged me with a grocery cart.
警官 法律上这责任怎么算
Sergeant, where does the law stand on liability there?
我不对购物车发表评论
I don't comment on carts.
谢谢你送他回家
Thank you for bringing him home.
我得和我爸再谈谈
Dad and I are gonna have another talk
去养老院的事
about assisted living.
我不需要人照顾 我是个成年人
I don't need assistance. I'm a grown man.
把我关到那里也阻止不了我死亡 儿子
Putting me there is not gonna stop me from dying, son.
那儿就是等死的地方
People go there to die.
天哪 你遇上杀猪盘了
For God's sake, you were catfished.
他在胡说八道什么
What the hell is he talking about?
网恋诈骗
It's a romance scam.
在网上伪装身份骗人
Uh, people online pretending to be someone else.
谢丽尔才不是骗子
Cheryl is not a scammer.
是吗
Really?
你给她转了六百美元 爸
You sent her $600, Dad.
她值得坐头等舱
She deserves to fly first-class.
你真觉得她会为了你 跨越大半个国家飞来
Y-You really think that she flew across the country for you?
我觉得
I did.
比尔
Bill?
Bill...
谢丽尔
Cheryl.
你找到她了
You found her.
在到达厅外面等着呢
Waiting outside arrivals.
我可没想到 来接我的会是警车
Well, I wasn't expecting to be picked up in a police car.
相信我 这已经算好的了
Trust me, it could have been worse.
- 你是真人 - 本人比网上
- You're real? - And even more
- 更漂亮 - 嘴可真甜
- lovely in person. - Oh, such a charmer.
你们俩是怎么认识的
How did you guys meet?
网络 你有空也该试试
The Internet. You ought to try it sometime.
警官们 非常感谢你们
Uh, Officers? Thank you so much
把事情都处理得这么妥当
for everything you've done to square things away here.
也替我儿子跟你们道个歉
And I apologize for my son.
不用道歉
No apology needed.
你有个非常关心你的儿子
You have a son who really cares about you.
你知道我只是关心你 对吧 爸
You know that's all it is, Dad, right?
好吧 如果你真的关心我
Well, if you care,
明天就去警局把我的割草机弄出来
tomorrow, get my lawn mower out of police impound.
还有 要是不想留一辈子心理阴影
And unless you want to be scarred for life,
今晚就别再打开那些摄像头了
don't even think about turning those cameras back on tonight.
总要有长大的一天
they got to grow up sometime.
各位 再见
Bye, guys.
- 再见 - 很快会再见的
- See you. - We'll see you soon,
好吗
okay?
我走之前 还有什么需要帮忙的吗
Unless you need anything before I leave.
没有了 回家好好休息吧
Nah. Go home, get some rest.
我感觉已经休息得很好了 但还是谢谢你
I'm feeling pretty rested, but thanks.
可怜的孩子
Poor kid.
可怜 我们擦消防车的时候
Poor kid? We're scrubbing the rigs
- 他窝在沙发上歇着 - 嘿
- and he's sitting on the couch. - Hey.
他看起来并不享受
It's not like he's enjoying it.
愁眉苦脸的
He looks miserable.
换作是我 估计也开心不起来
I guess I'd be miserable, too.
学校的尖子生来坐冷板凳
Academy superstar to benchwarmer.
为什么奇米要用泡泡纸把他包起来
Why do we think Chim's got him in Bubble Wrap?
可能只是想让他慢慢适应工作
He's probably just trying to ease him into the job.
先安排些轻松的活
Put him on light duty for now.
这活再轻松点 他都要飘走了
If he was on any lighter duty, he'd float away.
得有人和奇米谈谈
Yeah, someone needs to talk to Chim.
好主意
Good idea.
不要 我再也不干这事了
No. No, I am not doing this again.
我可不是我姐夫的监护人
I am not my brother-in-law's keeper.
可总得有人去说啊
Well, somebody needs to be.
我知道该找谁了
I think I know who.
她来了
There she is.
我们得谈谈
We gotta talk.
我就怕这个
I was afraid of that.
这酒不错
Nice bottle.
我在哪看到过 说它效果好
I read somewhere that it's good
应对突发状况
for, uh, flare-ups.
说吧
So?
谁又抱怨了
Who complained?
谁没抱怨
Who didn't?
大家都挺担心的
Everyone's concerned.
担心我对那孩子太严厉了
What, that I'm too hard on the kid?
担心你在步我们老队长的后尘
That you're following in footsteps of our old captain.
巴比可不是那么好超越的
Bobby is a tough act to follow.
不是巴比
Not Bobby.
是杰拉德
Captain Gerrard.
什么
What?
我从杰拉德那学到的 一是羡慕他的胡子
The only thing I got from Gerrard is mustache envy
二是练就了刷厕所的绝活
and a PhD in "scrubbing the crapper."
听着 他也让你坐过冷板凳
Listen, he also benched you.
还有我
And me.
让我们闲了那么久
Kept us out of the action so long
久到都忘了自己当初为什么要当消防员
we wondered why we signed up in the first place.
他让我们削土豆 还把地板擦得锃亮
He had us peeling potatoes and spit shining the floors.
哈利现在连拖把都没碰过呢
Harry hasn't even touched a mop.
这反而更糟
Even worse.
怎么就更糟了
How is that even worse?
哈里加入118分队
Harry signed up for the 118,
但你却不让他成为团队一员
but you won't let him be on the team.
你知道杰拉德第一次
Do you know what happened the first time
让我进火场时发生了什么吗
Gerrard let me on a structure fire?
- 可奇米 - 我失去了我的兄弟
- But Chim - I lost a brother!
去年 我们又失去了一位朋友
Last year, we lost a friend!
亨 每次哈里用那种菜鸟一样的
Hen, every time Harry looks at me with those probie
可怜巴巴的眼神看着我 我就忍不住
puppy dog eyes, I can't help it.
我满脑子都是  巴比的继子
I just see all the ways that Bobby's stepson
雅典娜的儿子 可能会在我的眼皮底下牺牲
Athena's son could die on my watch.
他不仅仅是谁家的孩子
He's not just someone's kid.
还是别的
Not anymore.
你的菜鸟
He's your probie.
他是你的责任 奇米
He's your responsibility, Chim.
我知道 所以我才想保护他
I know that. That's why I'm trying to protect him.
但你不能用泡泡纸把他包起来
But you can't protect him in Bubble Wrap.
他需要历练 因为这工作随时会要了他的命
He needs experiences because this job can kill him.
他需要的是一位能教他 带他
He needs a captain who's gonna show him
让他学会如何活下去的队长
and teach him how to stay alive.
可如果我做不到呢
What if I can't?
那就放他走
Then cut him loose.
其他消防站会抢着要他的
Some other firehouse will be lucky to have him.
他属于118消防队
He belongs at the 118.
那就让他上 教练
Then put him in, Coach.
你坐哪儿
Who do you sit next to?
哪有空位就坐哪儿
Whoever is on the bus.
所以 没有固定座位
So, there's no assigned seating?
你坐过公交车吗
Have you ridden a bus?
放松点 伙计
Easy, pal.
把手机收起来 开始吃饭
Put your phone away and start eating.
现在方便聊聊吗
Is now a good time to talk?
我是不是打扰到你们了
I'm interrupting, aren't I?
其实 我们刚坐下来准备吃晚饭
Actually, we were just sitting down for dinner.
你们吃什么
What are you having?
所以 过渡性住房的伙食怎么样
So, how's the grub at the transitional house?
艾丽克斯说那边养了鸡
Alex said they have chickens.
不是拿来吃的
Mm. Not to eat.
你多大了
How old are you?
十五岁
Fifteen.
你在法庭上说你有个孩子时
Hmm. When you said in court you had a kid,
我还以为他五六岁呢
I assumed he was five or six.
我的意思是 你太年轻了
I mean, you're so young.
他倒也没那么年轻
He's not that young.
我当爸比较早
I got an early start.
你告诉艾丽克斯你要来这里了吗
Did you tell Alex that you were gonna be here?
需要这么做吗
Is that how it works?
我去哪儿都得向她报备吗
Do I need to tell her everywhere I go?
谁是艾丽克斯
Who's Alex?
艾丽克斯是
Alex is
帮助阿比盖尔的人
helping Abigail.
她是我在洛杉矶警察局的同事
She's a colleague of mine at the LAPD.
仅此而已
Is that all?
什么意思
What do you mean?
没什么 她真的很漂亮
I don't know. She's really pretty.
真的吗
She is?
我来收拾这些
I'm gonna clear these.
别 不用你帮忙 好吗
Oh, no. Do not help. All right?
我家 我来收拾
My house, my mess.
做饭和洗碗
Dinner and dishes.
克里斯托弗真幸运
Christopher's lucky.
你简直是个完美的爸爸
You're, like, a perfect dad.
我还差得远
Oh, I'm far from perfect.
我都不送我儿子上学了
I don't even drive my son to school anymore.
克里斯坐公交车
Chris takes the bus.
他嘴上说想要自由 可其实
Says he wants freedom, but really,
是我太忙了 连轴转上二十四小时班
I'm too busy just working 24-hour shifts
连放学接他都抽不出时间
to show my face at pickup.
我父母被无罪释放了
My parents got acquitted.
什么
What?
所有指控都不成立
On all charges.
地方检察官打的电话
The D.A. called.
这怎么可能
How is that possible?
有辆教会的车
All I know is a ministry van
去监狱把他们接走了
came and picked them up from the prison.
他们能回到以前的生活
They get to go back to their old lives.
而我却什么都没有
I get nothing.
我真的很抱歉 阿比盖尔
I am so sorry, Abigail.
时间不早了
Uh, it's-it's getting pretty late,
而且开车回帕萨迪纳要很久
and it's a long drive back to Pasadena.
或许
Maybe...
要是不打扰的话
Only if I'm not imposing.
抱歉 你说什么
Uh, I'm sorry, what?
哦 我
Oh, I...
我以为你在邀请我留宿
I thought you were inviting me to stay the night.
- 不 - 睡沙发就行
- No. - On the couch, obviously.
我是说 你开车回去没问题吧
I meant, are you okay to drive?
当然
Of course.
没问题
U-Uh, yes.
不打扰你们了
I'll leave you alone.
对不起 我太蠢了
I'm so sorry. I'm so dumb.
- 但 - 没关系 阿比盖尔
- But - It's fine. Abigail.
你不蠢
You're not dumb.
而且你不是一个人 好吗
And you're not alone, okay?
- 记住了吗 - 好
- Remember that? - Okay.
哈里
Harry.
巴克说只要我不碰刀 就没事
Buck said it was okay as long as I don't touch the knives.
过来 跟你说句话
Yeah. A word.
去吧 这里我来收拾就好
Go. I'll finish up here.
坐吧
Have a seat.
你知道我也曾是这个消防站的菜鸟队员 对吧
So, you know I was a probie in this firehouse, right?
在二十年前
20 years ago?
我在这里的第一年
My first year here,
是我职业生涯中最糟糕的一年
that was the worst year of my career.
也许是我人生中最糟糕的一年
Maybe my life.
队长 我不知道自己哪里做错了
Look, Cap, I don't know what I did wrong,
但你告诉我 我马上改
but if you tell me, I can fix it.
你没做错任何事 哈里 实际上
You haven't done anything wrong, Harry. In fact,
你几乎什么都没做 这是我的问题
you haven't really done much of anything, which is my fault.
你知道吗 我当菜鸟的时候
You see, when I was a probie,
有一阵子 我的队长就只让我收拾桌子
for a while, all my cap let me do was clear tables.
像个高级服务员
I was like a glorified busboy.
真的很难不往心里去
It was really hard not to take that personally.
我想说的是
What I'm saying is...
问题不在你 孩子 在我
...you're not the problem, kid. I am.
我当年很幸运 这里有个人
You see, I was lucky enough that there was someone
愿意给我一个机会
here who gave me a chance.
你现在也需要一个人
What you need is someone
该死
Damn it.
没事的 你回来再跟我说就好
It's okay. You can tell me when you get back.
你需要的是有人愿意给你一个机会
What you need is someone to take a chance on you.
来吧 哈里
Come on, Harry.
真的吗
You sure?
在我改变主意之前 快上车
Get in the rig before I change my mind.
走吧 菜鸟
Let's go, rookie.
快点 菜鸟
Hurry up, probie.
洛杉矶消防局云梯消防车
那辆着火的是你的垃圾车吗
That your garbage truck on fire?
是的 我本想卸货 但液压系统卡住了
Yeah. I tried to empty my load, but my hydraulics seized.
垃圾就烧起来了 这东西冒烟
The garbage is on fire. How long has this thing
- 多久了 - 大概是
- been smoking? - I think I noticed it
- 二十分钟前发现的 - 二十分钟分钟 收到
- like 20 minutes ago. - 20 minutes. Copy that.
队长 它在呼吸
Hey, Cap, it's breathing.
一旦接触到空气 就会
When this fire finally gets some air, it's gonna
- 回燃 - 我们可以切开货厢
- Back draft. - We can cut the pits,
打开挡板
open the tailgate
把着火的垃圾全倒到街上
and dump all the burning trash into the street.
不行 它烧得太久了
No, it's been burning too long.
现在让它接触氧气 会直接变成炸弹
We introduce oxygen right now, that trash turns into a bomb.
那隔绝氧气灭火
How about we starve it?
如果我们想把卡车
If we want to lose the truck
和整条街都赔进去 就这么干
and the whole block, sure.
我在消防学院的最后一周见过这种情况
Look, I saw this in my last week at the academy.
火要是烧得够猛
If that fire burns hot enough,
就会烧到油箱
it's gonna reach the diesel tanks,
甚至是液压管
maybe even the hydraulic lines.
是啊 看哪个先到
Yeah, or whichever one comes first.
然后 砰
And then boom.
好了 疏散所有人
All right, let's clear everyone out.
设置一百英尺的警戒区
I want a 100-foot perimeter.
收到 路锥马上到
Copy that. Cones on the way.
好 上一点五英寸的水带
All right, fire up a one and three-quarter inch line
配上穿刺喷头
with a piercing nozzle.
对垃圾进行间接攻击
I want an indirect attack on that trash
先把内部温度降下来
to cool things down in there.
- 行动 - 收到 队长
- Let's move! - Copy you, Cap.
- 马上来 - 嘿
- On it! - Hey!
哈里
Hey, Harry!
- 哈里 - 安全第一
- Harry! - Safety first.
对吧 队长
Right, Cap?
对 安全第一
Right. Safety first.
我们准备好了
We're ready.
好的 收到
All right, copy that.
- 队长 就位了 - 准备好了
- Yeah, Cap, we're in. - Ready here.
打开红色水带
All right, open the red line.
巴克 情况如何
Buck, how we looking?
快好了
Yeah, almost there.
队长 已经好了
Okay, Cap, we got conversion.
拔掉插销 打开挡板
Let's cut the pin. Pop the tailgate.
换两英寸半的水带灭火
I want a two and a half inch on that trash.
哈里 把垃圾钩给我
Harry, get me those rubbish hooks.
哈里
Harry!
Harry?
帕尼卡 把钩子给我
Panikkar, grab me the hooks.
你能搞定吗
You good on this?
- 快 - 交给我们 队长
- Go! - We got it, Cap.
哈里
Harry.
等等 别开车
Wait. Don't drive!
哈里
Harry!
所有人停车
Everybody, stop driving!
哈里
Harry?
Harry!
哈里 该死
Harry? Damn it.
停车
Stop driving!
所有人停车
Everybody, stop driving.
队长 你还好吗
Hey, Cap, you okay?
嗯
Yeah.
巴克 埃迪 去看看司机
Buck, Eddie, check the driver.
好 来吧
Okay. Here.
你去哪了
Where were you?
我在外围 拦着那些人
I was at the perimeter. I was holding those people back.
你真没事吧 队长
You sure you're okay, Cap?
嗯
Yeah.
疑似轻微中风 无明显外伤
Possible minor stroke. Doesn't appear to be injured.
我和他半斤八两
That makes two of us.
干得好 菜鸟
Good job, probie.
谢谢 队长
Thanks, Cap.
我需要你回去
All right, I need you guys back!
各位干得漂亮
Good job, everyone. All right.
格兰特 你要去哪儿
Grant. You going somewhere?
我想去拿点零食吃
Yeah, I was just gonna grab a snack.
你觉得现在是吃零食的时候吗 菜鸟
You think snacking is a good use of your time, probie?
去把厕所刷了
Go scrub the crapper.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
欢迎加入118分队 小子
And welcome to the 118, kid.
谢谢
Thank you.
把厕所刷了
Scrub that crapper!
嘿
Hey.
你那边怎么样了
How's it going over there?
最后一个  弄完我就走
Uh, last one, and then I will get out of your hair.
好了
All right.
- 你们俩玩得开心 - 好啊
- Ah. Have fun, you two. - Ah, good.
那肯定的
Oh, we will. We will.
嗷呜 霸王龙老爸
Grr! Dadasaurus Rex
出没啦
is on the loose.
恐龙防护罩 今天过得怎么样
Dino-proof. Ah! How was your day?
挺好的 不过感觉你们过得更开心
Uh, it was good, but I think yours might have been better.
- 嗨 - 值班很顺利
- Hi. - Well, shift went well,
还陪这两个小家伙搭了个堡垒
plus, I got to build a fort with these two.
还有比这更美的事吗
Who can ask for more than that?
咱们晚饭前把这里收拾一下
Let's clean this up before dinner.
才不要
Never!
所以 哈里还好吗
So, Harry was all right?
何止是好
More than all right.
这孩子虽说年纪小
You know, the kid is young,
但我觉得他天生就是干这行的料
but I think he has what it takes.
这么说 你再也不会做噩梦了
So, no more nightmares?
而且他还救了我一命
Uh-huh. Plus, he saved my life.
等等 你差点出事 奇米
Wait, your life was in danger? Chimney?
看看你 你开窍了
Look at you. You're getting it. -
你开窍了
You're getting it. Whoa.
妈 放开我 我自己来
Mom, let me go. I got it.
超级里德登场
It's SuperReid!
你绝对想不到
You wouldn't believe
我擦完之后那玩意有多亮
the shine on that thing when I was done.
没想到你当消防员的第一周
Wow. I mean, I wasn't expecting your first week as a firefighter
会用到这么多清洁剂
to involve so many cleaning products.
梅 这是菜鸟的日常
That's the life of a probie, May.
虽说不怎么光鲜 但都很重要
It's not all glamorous, but it's all important.
说实话
Personally,
很庆幸 今天早上
I appreciate that I learned three new uses
- 学到了白醋的三个新用法 - 不是吧
- for white vinegar this morning. - No.
这才哪到哪 你们现在笑吧
You know what? It's all good. You laugh now,
等我把洗碗机里面擦得锃亮
but just you wait until I make the interior
你们就知道厉害了
of that dishwasher shine.
先别急
Mm. Not so fast.
我们有东西要给你
We have something for you.
本来想在你第一天上班前
We wanted to give this to you
就给你的
before your first day,
结果你没给我们机会
but you didn't give us a chance.
巴比的刀
Bobby's knife.
我们希望你在身上带着点
We wanted you to have a little piece
他的东西
of him to carry with you.
谢谢你们
Thank you, guys.
我很喜欢
I love it.
他会为你感到骄傲的 哈里
He would've been so proud of you, Harry.
那另一个盒子里是什么 毕竟
So, what's in the other box? I mean,
第一个礼物已经很难超越了
first one's kind of a hard act to follow.
要是巴比还在 也一定会送给你的
Well, this is what Bobby would have given you, if he were here.
他会希望你有一把自己的刀
He'd want you to have your own knife.
活成独当一面的自己
And let you be your own man.
真希望他在这里
I wish he were here.
他一直都在
He is.
克里斯托弗
Christopher.
阿比盖尔
Abigail?
你怎么会在这里
What are you doing here?
你爸爸上班忙
Your dad's busy at work.
让我来接你
He asked me to come get you.
好的
Oh, okay.
走吧 我的车就在那边
Okay. My car's just over there, okay?
冬奥停播 下集将于2月26日回归